<p><b>Terms Of Use</b></p>


<br/><p><b>1.</b><br/>
The use is possible after registrating using the registration form. The user assures that all informations are complete and correct.The operator can not guarantee the actual availiability of the internet access.
</p>

<br/><p><b>2.</b><br/>
The use is provided with the existing technical possibilities. In particular, the user has not the right to use the internet in a particular way or for a certain period.
</p>

<br/><p><b>3.</b><br/>
Any liability, especially for warranty and damages (excepted for intent and personal injury) are excluded. Moreover, the operator does not assume liability for the contents of accessed websites and downloaded files or for possible virus infection while using the internet. The user acknowledges to know that the operator provides exclusive the access to the internet, but no virus protection or firewall.
</p>

<br/><p><b>4.</b><br/>
It is permitted to access websites with illegal content and to publish illegal or legally protected content.
</p>

<br/><p><b>5.</b><br/>
It is specifically prohibited to use the internet to download or distribute in any way content which is protected by copyright.
</p>

<br/><p><b>6.</b><br/>
Any improper use of the Internet, especially the utilisation that may bring legal consequences to the operator or third parties, is prohibited.
</p>

<br/><p><b>7.</b><br/>
If the operator has to transfer a title to insurance benefits to a third party due to the user's activities, the user is obligated to indemnify and hold the operator harmless in respect of legal proceedings and claims.
</p>

<br/><p><b>8.</b><br/>
In the case of violating these terms of use or of suspect the operator reserves the right to block the account without giving reasons. We do not assume liability for data loss.
</p>

<br/><p><b>9.</b><br/>
The asked information serve as verification, so that internet abuse can be avoided. Furthermore, we use the geographical and statistical information to improve our and our sponsors' services. We guarantee that the personal information is only used internally and will not be passed to third parties without permission.
</p>

<br/><p><b>10.</b><br/>
If a provision of these terms of use is or becomes illegal, invalid or unenforceable in any jurisdiction, that shall not affect.
</p>